JENN JUNOD

Developer Advocate | Curious | Human Connecter hello@teachjenntech.com • teachjenntech.com

ABOUT

As, someone who thrives on human connection, I know how to advocate for those who have gone unheard. My passion and experience create a space where people can come together.

I am a developer advocate, international speaker, MC (Emcee), podcast host, and live streamer.

EXPERIENCE

Gravitee Aug 2022 - Oct 2022

Developer Advocate Consultant

Gravitee offers API development, security, management, observability, and productization within one platform.

- Grew brand awareness via events, blog posts, and conferences
- Created and distributed product demo videos internally with 80% view rate
- Increased unique visitors to Gravitee community by 42%, and page views by 100% by promoting Gravitee at Denver Startup Week

Teach Jenn Tech July 2022 - Present

Developer Advocate

Livestream, where technology experts teach Jenn about different technical/programming topics.

- Has grown developer audience from 40 to 1250+ on Twitter in less than 120 days
- Over 1000% Growth Rate Has produced 30+ episodes at a rate of 3-4 videos per week
- Top performing topics: APIs, JavaScript, TypeScript, and Python

API Denver Meetup Group

May 2022 - Present

Co-Organizer

Network & learn what professionals in Denver are using to build and consume APIs to drive their business.

- Facilitates events for 20 attendees including food/drink
- Builds relationships with companies in the API industry to speak at Denver API Meetups
- Manages community, graphic creation & distributes content for social media

Sh!t You Don't Want to Talk About

Nov 2021 - Present

Podcast Host

Sh!t You Don't Want to Talk About is a place people can come to find hope and healing, to know they are not alone, and to finally be heard.

Stoplight Jan 2021 - Jan 2022

Stoplight is a collaborative API design platform

Learning Services Manager

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022

- Developed training programs that would have launched Q2 2022
- Defined training curriculum and coordinated the creation of content
- Tracked KPIs of employee training on products and progress

Sales Enablement Manager

Jan 2021 - July 2021

- Created processes for sales to complete contracts, legal reviews, customer outreach tools, and complete migration initiatives
- Worked with sales leadership to evaluate coaching opportunities across the team
- Worked cross-functionally with product and marketing to ensure a successful IT project, ensuring salespeople are properly trained on the new tools

JENN JUNOD

Developer Advocate | Curious | Human Connecter hello@teachjenntech.com • teachjenntech.com

EXPERIENCE cont'd

Pro One Media Productions

Oct 2019 - Dec 2020

Digital Production & Project Manager

Pro One Media Productions, Inc., is a full-service production company, specializing in corporate and commercial work and associated marketing services.

- Managed communications and logistics between multiple teams: AV production, videography editing,
 & web development
- Hired, trained, and managed the Control Room Team of Virtual Tech Directors, Studio Technicians, and Virtual Production/Customer Success Managers
- Built and nurtured revenue-critical relationships with key clients to enhance loyalty and retention
- Coordinated teams to complete registration, website development, and steps leading to Virtual and/or Hybrid events

GoDaddy Inc. 2015-2019

GoDaddy is the world's largest services platform for entrepreneurs around the globe, giving them all the help and tools they need to grow online.

International Communication and Incentives Project Manager

- Recruited, hired, and managed top-level talent for various job positions
- Planned and publicized events, including negotiating vendor contracts and designing promotional materials
- Facilitated growth and increased brand awareness by working with the sales team to build and maintain key business relationships during the acquisition
- Made changes to the project scope and cost and implemented the most effective change management processes
- Oversaw change management issues related to organizational changes, policy, and procedure implementations

Sales and Customer Support Supervisor

- Oversaw training of new team members and mentored each to promote productivity, accuracy, and friendly service
- Capitalized on opportunities to enhance customer experiences and bring in repeat business
- Excelled in change management such as changes to compensation, organization structure, and policies
- Spearheaded educational training workshops and product presentations

TRAINING & CERTIFICATIONS

- StartingBloc (Los Angeles 2015 Fellow).
- U & Improved (Leader 5/2013, Communicator 6/2013, Warrior 9/2013)
- Landmark Forum, Advanced Course, Self-Expression & Leadership Program, & Integrity: The Bottom Line (2016)

SKILLS

- Content creation- blog, video, live streaming, podcasts, and TwitterSpaces
- Cross-Functional Team Collaboration
- Community Management, including Change Management, and Customer-first Mindset
- Entrepreneurial mindset